

# Cheng Yuen Pui

#### PROGRAMMER · INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Flat 2, 14/F, Lai Chung House, Mei Chung Court, Tai Wai, Shatin, NT

🛘 (+852) 67386569 | 💌 chengyuenpui1234@gmail.com | 🖸 kittychengyuenpui | 🛅 kitty-cheng-a20937171

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

## **Summary**

Currently working as IT Programmer at CMA Testing. 2 years experience specializing in front-end and in-house web application development. Familiar with C#. Net and utilizing Microsoft Graph API on projects. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if needed.

# Work Experience \_

#### **CMA Testing (CMA Industrial Development Foundation Limited)**

https://www.cmatesting.org/

July 2019 - Now

PROGRAMMER

- · Develop, maintain and enhance in-house system applications and websites
- Assist in requirement study, analysis and design with different parties
- Prepare system documentation, system support and troubleshooting on the developed systems
- Implemented several API microservices in Node.js Koa and in the serverless AWS Lambda functions.
- Deployed a centralized logging environment (ELK, Filebeat, CloudWatch, S3) which gather log data from docker containers and AWS resources.
- Deployed a centralized monitoring environment(Grafana, InfluxDB, CollectD) which gather system metrics as well as docker run-time metrics.

#### **WWF (World Wide Fund for Nature Hong Kong)**

https://www.wwf.org.hk/

INTERNSHIP

• Assisted in a blockchain project for sustainable fashion

• Built an online questionnaire with PHP code on 000WebHost for mobile devices to show different results after submission according to the answers chosen by a respondent

Star Fantasy https://www.starfantasy.net/

NTP XSPORT HELPER (PART-TIME JOB)

Aug. 2015 - Sep. 2015

Aug. 2018 - Mar. 2019

• Provided relevant information for visitors and answered their questions with problem-solving skills

#### **Education**

#### The Hong Kong Polytechnic University

2.65 Award GPA

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (HONOURS) IN COMPUTING

Sep. 2016 - Aug. 2019

- Studied courses related to Computer Science, database concepts, information systems knowledge
- Applied computing theories and programming methodologies in projects and assignments

#### **HKUSPACE Community College**

3.56 Graduation GPA

ASSOCIATE OF ENGINEERING (COMPUTER SCIENCE)

Sep. 2014 - Aug. 2016

- · Studied courses related to the field of Computer Science, programming skills, logical thinking and problem-solving skills are learned
- Applied problem-solving skills in projects and assignments

### Skills

Programming languages, Familiar with C, C++, HTML, CSS, Java, SQL, PHP, and JavaScript, C#,

CoffeeScript, Angular

Computer software, Capable of using MS Word, Excel, and PowerPoint

Computer Systems, Familiar with Windows and Linux

Languages, Fluent in Cantonese, English, and Mandarin

AUGUST 21, 2023 · RESUME · 1